[
  {
    "question": "System Requirement is a not structured document setting out detailed descriptions of the system’s functions, services and operational constraints",
    "choices": [
      "True",
      "False"
    ],
    "answer": "False"
  },
  {
    "question": "Domain Requirements is constraints on the system from the dominant operation of the system.",
    "choices": [
      "True",
      "False"
    ],
    "answer": "False"
  },
  {
    "question": "Non-Functional Requirements often apply to the system as a whole rather than individual features or services.",
    "choices": [
      "True",
      "False"
    ],
    "answer": "True"
  },
  {
    "question": "Functional Requirements is a statements of services the system should provide, how the system should react to particular inputs and how the system should behave in particular situations.",
    "choices": [
      "True",
      "False"
    ],
    "answer": "True"
  },
  {
    "question": "Structured specifications this works well for some types of requirements e.g. requirements for embedded control system but is sometimes too rigid for writing business system requirements.",
    "choices": [
      "True",
      "False"
    ],
    "answer": "True"
  },
  {
    "question": "This might include graphical system models showing the relationships between the system components and the system and its environment.",
    "choices": [
      "System models",
      "System evolution",
      "System Index"
    ],
    "answer": "System models"
  },
  {
    "question": "External Requirements which arise from factors which are external to the system and its development process e.g. interoperability requirements, legislative requirements, et.",
    "choices": [
      "True",
      "False"
    ],
    "answer": "True"
  },
  {
    "question": "User Requirement is a statements in natural language plus diagrams of the services the system provides and its operational constraints.",
    "choices": [
      "True",
      "False"
    ],
    "answer": "True"
  },
  {
    "question": "Organisational and political factors may not influence the system requirements.",
    "choices": [
      "True",
      "False"
    ],
    "answer": "False"
  },
  {
    "question": "Organisational and political factors may influence the system requirements.",
    "choices": [
      "True",
      "False"
    ],
    "answer": "True"
  },
  {
    "question": "Formal or informal interviews with stakeholders are not part of most RE processes.",
    "choices": [
      "True",
      "False"
    ],
    "answer": "False"
  },
  {
    "question": "Scene in the system are real-life examples of how a system can be used.",
    "choices": [
      "True",
      "False"
    ],
    "answer": "False"
  },
  {
    "question": "Requirements management planning establishes the level of requirements management detail that is required.",
    "choices": [
      "True",
      "False"
    ],
    "answer": "True"
  },
  {
    "question": "Requirements Engineering is an iterative activity in which these processes are interleaved.",
    "choices": [
      "True",
      "False"
    ],
    "answer": "True"
  },
  {
    "question": "Checking there any requirements conflicts.",
    "choices": [
      "Consistency",
      "Validity",
      "Completeness"
    ],
    "answer": "Consistency"
  },
  {
    "question": "The requirements be implemented given available budget and technology.",
    "choices": [
      "Completeness",
      "Validity",
      "Realism"
    ],
    "answer": "Realism"
  },
  {
    "question": "The requirements can be checked.",
    "choices": [
      "Validity",
      "Realism",
      "Verifiability"
    ],
    "answer": "Verifiability"
  },
  {
    "question": "Problems of requirements analysis stakeholders doesn’t know what they really want.",
    "choices": [
      "True",
      "False"
    ],
    "answer": "True"
  },
  {
    "question": "Requirements engineering is the process of establishing the services that the customer requires from a system and the constraints under which it operates and is developed.",
    "choices": [
      "True",
      "False"
    ],
    "answer": "True"
  },
  {
    "question": "Natural Language is a requirements written using numbered sentences and each sentence should express two requirements.",
    "choices": [
      "True",
      "False"
    ],
    "answer": "True"
  },
  {
    "question": "Design description languages is an approach that use for interface and hardware and software specifications.",
    "choices": [
      "True",
      "False"
    ],
    "answer": "True"
  },
  {
    "question": "Structured specifications is not works well for some types of requirements e.g. requirements for embedded control system but is sometimes too rigid for writing business system requirements.",
    "choices": [
      "True",
      "False"
    ],
    "answer": "False"
  },
  {
    "question": "Domain specialists understand the area so well that they do not think of making the domain requirements explicit.",
    "choices": [
      "Product requirements",
      "Implicitness",
      "Understandability"
    ],
    "answer": "Implicitness"
  },
  {
    "question": "Requirement is a range from a low-level abstract statement of a service or of a system constraint to a detailed mathematical functional specification.",
    "choices": [
      "True",
      "False"
    ],
    "answer": "True"
  },
  {
    "question": "System Requirements Specification should not describe the functional and nonfunctional requirements in more detail.",
    "choices": [
      "True",
      "False"
    ],
    "answer": "False"
  },
  {
    "question": "Different stakeholders and customers may have conflicting requirements",
    "choices": [
      "True",
      "False"
    ],
    "answer": "True"
  },
  {
    "question": "Requirements management is the process of managing changing views and plans during the requirements engineering process and system development.",
    "choices": [
      "True",
      "False"
    ],
    "answer": "False"
  },
  {
    "question": "These interviews are based on pre-determined list of questions",
    "choices": [
      "Effective interview",
      "Open interviews",
      "Closed interviews"
    ],
    "answer": "Closed interviews"
  },
  {
    "question": "These interviews where various issues are explored with stakeholders.",
    "choices": [
      "Effective interview",
      "Closed interviews",
      "Open interviews"
    ],
    "answer": "Open interviews"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Scenarios?",
    "choices": [
      "Prompt the interviewee to get discussions going using a springboard question, a requirements proposal, or by working together on a prototype system.",
      "Interaction is with system stakeholders from managers to external regulators.",
      "are real-life examples of how a system can be used."
    ],
    "answer": "are real-life examples of how a system can be used."
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Scope of Ethnography?",
    "choices": [
      "Requirements that are derived from the way that people actually work rather than the way I which process definitions suggest that they ought to work.",
      "The problem with ethnography is that it studies existing practices which may have some historical basis which is no longer relevant.",
      "Social and organisational factors of importance may be observed"
    ],
    "answer": "Requirements that are derived from the way that people actually work rather than the way I which process definitions suggest that they ought to work."
  },
  {
    "question": "Requirements Engineering is an optional activity in which these processes are interleaved.",
    "choices": [
      "True",
      "False"
    ],
    "answer": "False"
  },
  {
    "question": "Using an executable model of the system to check requirements.",
    "choices": [
      "Test-case generation",
      "Requirements review",
      "Prototyping"
    ],
    "answer": "Prototyping"
  },
  {
    "question": "Requirements elicitation and analysis sometimes called requirements elicitation or requirements discovery.",
    "choices": [
      "True",
      "False"
    ],
    "answer": "True"
  },
  {
    "question": "Functional Requirements is a statements of services the system should provide, what the system should not react to particular inputs and what the system should not behave in particular situations.",
    "choices": [
      "True",
      "False"
    ],
    "answer": "False"
  },
  {
    "question": "In practice, requirements and design are inseparable.",
    "choices": [
      "True",
      "False"
    ],
    "answer": "True"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Software Requirements document?",
    "choices": [
      "Is the official statement of what is required of the system developers",
      "Applies to the system as a whole rather than individual features or services.",
      "Defines what should be implemented so may be part of a contract between client and contractor."
    ],
    "answer": "Is the official statement of what is required of the system developers"
  },
  {
    "question": "Systems normally have a range of customers.",
    "choices": [
      "True",
      "False"
    ],
    "answer": "True"
  },
  {
    "question": "Scenarios are real-life examples of how a system can be used.",
    "choices": [
      "True",
      "False"
    ],
    "answer": "True"
  },
  {
    "question": "Groups related requirements and organises them into coherent clusters.",
    "choices": [
      "Requirements discovery",
      "Requirements classification and organisation",
      "Prioritisation and negotiation"
    ],
    "answer": "Requirements classification and organisation"
  },
  {
    "question": "All functions required by the customer included.",
    "choices": [
      "Completeness",
      "Consistency",
      "Validity"
    ],
    "answer": "Completeness"
  },
  {
    "question": "During this stage, the problem or the change proposal is analyzed to check that it is valid.",
    "choices": [
      "Problem analysis and change specification",
      "Change analysis and costing",
      "Change implementation"
    ],
    "answer": "Problem analysis and change specification"
  },
  {
    "question": "Non-Functional Requirements often apply to the system as one rather than dual features or services.",
    "choices": [
      "True",
      "False"
    ],
    "answer": "False"
  },
  {
    "question": "Functional Requirements may state what the system should not do.",
    "choices": [
      "True",
      "False"
    ],
    "answer": "True"
  },
  {
    "question": "Requirements engineering is the process of establishing the customer service but not requiring from the system and constraints.",
    "choices": [
      "True",
      "False"
    ],
    "answer": "False"
  },
  {
    "question": "Requirements are expressed in the language of the application domain",
    "choices": [
      "Understandability",
      "Implicitness",
      "Product requirements"
    ],
    "answer": "Understandability"
  },
  {
    "question": "External Requirements which not arise from factors which are external to the system and its development process e.g. interoperability requirements, legislative requirements, et.",
    "choices": [
      "True",
      "False"
    ],
    "answer": "False"
  },
  {
    "question": "Requirements Confusion Functional and non-functional requirements tend to be mixed-up.",
    "choices": [
      "True",
      "False"
    ],
    "answer": "True"
  },
  {
    "question": "User Requirement is a statements in programming language plus diagrams of the services the system provides and its operational constraints.",
    "choices": [
      "True",
      "False"
    ],
    "answer": "False"
  },
  {
    "question": "Tabular specification used to supplement unnatural language.",
    "choices": [
      "True",
      "False"
    ],
    "answer": "False"
  },
  {
    "question": "Requirements discovery the process of gathering information from customer and existing systems.",
    "choices": [
      "True",
      "False"
    ],
    "answer": "True"
  },
  {
    "question": "Formal or informal interviews with stakeholders are part of most RE processes.",
    "choices": [
      "True",
      "False"
    ],
    "answer": "True"
  },
  {
    "question": "The requirements document and, where necessary, the system design and implementation, are modified.",
    "choices": [
      "Problem analysis and change specification",
      "Change implementation",
      "Change analysis and costing"
    ],
    "answer": "Change implementation"
  },
  {
    "question": "Problems of requirements analysis stakeholders know what they really want.",
    "choices": [
      "True",
      "False"
    ],
    "answer": "False"
  },
  {
    "question": "System Requirement is structured document setting out detailed descriptions of the system’s functions, services and operational constraints.",
    "choices": [
      "True",
      "False"
    ],
    "answer": "True"
  },
  {
    "question": "Natural language specification requirements are written as natural language sentences supplemented by diagrams and tables.",
    "choices": [
      "True",
      "False"
    ],
    "answer": "True"
  },
  {
    "question": "Requirements which arise from factors which are external to the system and its development process e.g. interoperability requirements, legislative requirements, etc",
    "choices": [
      "Organisational requirements",
      "External requirements",
      "Product requirements"
    ],
    "answer": "External requirements"
  },
  {
    "question": "A statement using some measure that can be objectively tested.",
    "choices": [
      "Verifiable non-functional requirement",
      "Functional Requirement",
      "Non-Functional Requirement"
    ],
    "answer": "Verifiable non-functional requirement"
  },
  {
    "question": "Requirements Confusion Functional and non-functional is not requirements tend to be mixed-up.",
    "choices": [
      "True",
      "False"
    ],
    "answer": "False"
  },
  {
    "question": "Tabular specification used to supplement natural language.",
    "choices": [
      "True",
      "False"
    ],
    "answer": "True"
  },
  {
    "question": "The process of gathering information about the required and existing systems and distilling the user and system requirements from this information.",
    "choices": [
      "Requirements Specification",
      "Requirements discovery",
      "Requirements Elicitation"
    ],
    "answer": "Requirements discovery"
  },
  {
    "question": "The system provides the functions which best support the customer’s needs.",
    "choices": [
      "Completeness",
      "Validity",
      "Consistency"
    ],
    "answer": "Validity"
  },
  {
    "question": "The effect of the proposed change is assessed using traceability information and general knowledge of the system requirements.",
    "choices": [
      "Change analysis and costing",
      "Change implementation",
      "Problem analysis and change specification"
    ],
    "answer": "Change analysis and costing"
  },
  {
    "question": "Effective Interview Be open-minded, avoid pre-conceived ideas about the requirements and not willing to listen to stakeholders.",
    "choices": [
      "True",
      "False"
    ],
    "answer": "False"
  },
  {
    "question": "Functional Requirements may state what the system should do in overall systematic view.",
    "choices": [
      "True",
      "False"
    ],
    "answer": "False"
  },
  {
    "question": "Precision is difficult without making the document difficult to read.",
    "choices": [
      "Requirements confusion",
      "Requirements amalgamation",
      "Lack of clarity"
    ],
    "answer": "Lack of clarity"
  },
  {
    "question": "Prioritising requirements and resolving requirements conflicts.",
    "choices": [
      "Requirements classification and organisation",
      "Prioritisation and negotiation",
      "Requirements discovery"
    ],
    "answer": "Prioritisation and negotiation"
  },
  {
    "question": "Requirements elicitation and analytics sometimes called requirements elicitation or requirements discovery.",
    "choices": [
      "True",
      "False"
    ],
    "answer": "False"
  },
  {
    "question": "Different stakeholders may have conflicting requirements.",
    "choices": [
      "True",
      "False"
    ],
    "answer": "True"
  },
  {
    "question": "Requirements which specify that the delivered product must behave in a particular way e.g. execution speed, reliability, etc.",
    "choices": [
      "Organisational requirements",
      "External requirements",
      "Product requirements"
    ],
    "answer": "Product requirements"
  },
  {
    "question": "Requirement is a range from a high-level abstract statement of a service or of a system constraint to a detailed mathematical functional specification.",
    "choices": [
      "True",
      "False"
    ],
    "answer": "True"
  },
  {
    "question": "Requirements discovery the process of gathering information about the required and existing systems and distilling the user and system requirements from this information.",
    "choices": [
      "True",
      "False"
    ],
    "answer": "True"
  },
  {
    "question": "Requirements management is the process of managing changing requirements during the requirements engineering process and system development.",
    "choices": [
      "True",
      "False"
    ],
    "answer": "True"
  },
  {
    "question": "Developing tests for requirements to check testability.",
    "choices": [
      "Test-case generation",
      "Prototyping",
      "Requirements review"
    ],
    "answer": "Test-case generation"
  },
  {
    "question": "The requirements themselves are the descriptions of the system services and constraints that are non-generated during the requirements engineering process.",
    "choices": [
      "True",
      "False"
    ],
    "answer": "True"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Functional Requirements?",
    "choices": [
      "Defines what should be implemented so may be part of a contract between client and contractor.",
      "Describe functionality or system services.",
      "Often apply to the system as a whole rather than individual features or services."
    ],
    "answer": "Describe functionality or system services."
  },
  {
    "question": "Requirements reviews systematic manual analysis of the requirements.",
    "choices": [
      "True",
      "False"
    ],
    "answer": "True"
  },
  {
    "question": "Natural language specification requirements are written as old language sentences supplemented by diagrams and tables.",
    "choices": [
      "True",
      "False"
    ],
    "answer": "False"
  },
  {
    "question": "Requirements which are a consequence of organisational policies and procedures e.g. process standards used, implementation requirements, etc.",
    "choices": [
      "Organisational requirements",
      "Product requirements",
      "External requirements"
    ],
    "answer": "Organisational requirements"
  },
  {
    "question": "Functional and non-functional requirements tend to be mixed-up.",
    "choices": [
      "Requirements confusion",
      "Lack of clarity",
      "Requirements amalgamation"
    ],
    "answer": "Requirements confusion"
  },
  {
    "question": "System Requirements Specification should describe the functional and nonfunctional requirements in more detail.",
    "choices": [
      "True",
      "False"
    ],
    "answer": "True"
  },
  {
    "question": "Change implementation the requirements document and, where necessary, the system design and implementation, are modified.",
    "choices": [
      "True",
      "False"
    ],
    "answer": "True"
  },
  {
    "question": "Ambiguous requirements may be interpreted in different ways by developers and users.",
    "choices": [
      "Requirements imprecision",
      "Requirements engineering",
      "System Requirement"
    ],
    "answer": "Requirements imprecision"
  },
  {
    "question": "Design description languages this approach is now rarely used although it can be useful for interface specifications.",
    "choices": [
      "True",
      "False"
    ],
    "answer": "True"
  },
  {
    "question": "These define system properties and constraints e.g. reliability, response time and storage requirements. Constraints are I/O device capability, system representations, etc.",
    "choices": [
      "Non-Functional Requirements",
      "Functional Requirements",
      "System Requirements"
    ],
    "answer": "Non-Functional Requirements"
  },
  {
    "question": "Effective Interview Be open-minded, avoid pre-conceived ideas about the requirements and are willing to listen to stakeholders.",
    "choices": [
      "True",
      "False"
    ],
    "answer": "True"
  },
  {
    "question": "Several different requirements may be expressed together.",
    "choices": [
      "Requirements confusion",
      "Lack of clarity",
      "Requirements amalgamation"
    ],
    "answer": "Requirements amalgamation"
  },
  {
    "question": "Systematic manual analysis of the requirements.",
    "choices": [
      "Requirements review",
      "Test-case generation",
      "Prototyping"
    ],
    "answer": "Requirements review"
  },
  {
    "question": "Domain Requirements is constraints on the system from the domain of operation.",
    "choices": [
      "True",
      "False"
    ],
    "answer": "True"
  },
  {
    "question": "What is Ethnography?",
    "choices": [
      "A social scientist spends a considerable time observing and analysing how people actually work.",
      "Sequence diagrams may be used to add detail to use-cases by showing the sequence of event processing in the system.",
      "A set of use cases should describe all possible interactions with the system"
    ],
    "answer": "A social scientist spends a considerable time observing and analysing how people actually work."
  },
  {
    "question": "In practice, requirements and design are separable.",
    "choices": [
      "True",
      "False"
    ],
    "answer": "True"
  },
  {
    "question": "This is inevitable as requirements may serve a dual function.",
    "choices": [
      "True",
      "False"
    ],
    "answer": "True"
  },
  {
    "question": "Systems normally have a range of stakeholders.",
    "choices": [
      "True",
      "False"
    ],
    "answer": "True"
  },
  {
    "question": "This should describe the functional and nonfunctional requirements in more detail.",
    "choices": [
      "System requirements specification",
      "Introduction",
      "User requirements definition"
    ],
    "answer": "System requirements specification"
  },
  {
    "question": "Be open-minded, avoid pre-conceived ideas about the requirements and are willing to listen to stakeholders.",
    "choices": [
      "Closed interviews",
      "Effective interview",
      "Open interviews"
    ],
    "answer": "Effective interview"
  }
]